All right, everybody. Welcome back to
This Week in Startups. I'm your host,
Jason Caligan. With me today,
very lucky to have Devin Thomas with us.
Now, Devin, you and I met because you
came to Launch Festival, just like a
little event I do for founders. That's
the origin story here. Tell us how we
met and then we'll we'll talk about what
you're building.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, when I first came up
with the idea, I was kind of researching
some preceeded uh funds and I followed
you on X already. And I think you
tweeted actually you were like, "Oh, I'm
excited about uh what I'm going to be
doing for this project of mine, Founder
University, and and I just was like,
"Okay, this sounds like you're excited
about it, so let let me see if I can
sign up and be a part of it." And, you
know, I just reached out and then soon
as I kind of like engaged with you all,
then um you know, they were like, "Oh,
we have something up coming up called
LaunchFest if you're interested is doing
that as well." And uh so, yeah. And then
you were there. It was cool. It was a
great experience.
>> Amazing. Yes. And this is like one of my
key tenants is say yes. So I always tell
my team like just like if you meet a
founder just say yes to meeting just say
yes to having launch festival and
letting a bunch of founders come
together. You never know what could come
out of it. And uh you've got this great
starter uh obliteration. Maybe you could
explain what you're building, why it's
important.
>> Started obliteration like at the end of
last year. I was actually uh I built
like a home cluster GPU cluster and
actually I originally started kind of
serving the site from my home cluster at
home. But uh what what makes it
important is there's a whole bunch of uh
professionals and companies out there
that are essentially underserved or
unserved by the frontier labs because
whether they're in cyber or they're
doing biology research or they need
synthetic data or defense all these use
cases that essentially uh the frontier
labs are essentially shunning. And uh so
we our our kind of tenant is to try to
provide the best models that will allow
these these use cases to be unblocked.
And so we've had a lot of traction, a
lot of press uh all around that because
um maybe some people feel like uh we
these use cases shouldn't be unblocked,
but those professionals seem to be super
happy about it. So it's been going well.
>> All right. And before we go to a demo
here and talk about this really
important issue, I just want to take a
minute put my Plaude pin on. Uh, hey, if
your work depends on conversations,
interviews, meetings, calls, check out
plot at plot.twtwist. Use the code twist
for 10% off. Great partner of ours here.
And uh, so let's talk about it. Devon,
the frontier models have full access to
the latest and greatest large language
models. And then if you're in cyber
defense and you are let's say hugging
face and open AAI wants to do a series
of attacks uh you know whether intended
or not or they're testing or white hat
let's put it all aside they want to test
cyber they pick hugging face as a target
hugging face does not have access to
open AI's latest model they keep that
for themselves so hugging face if they
wanted to mount a defense against the
latest and greatest frontier models,
they don't have the same access to the
tools. Correct.
>> Exactly. Yep. And even if they have
access to those uh special cyber
programs, still there, many of them uh
our customers are still complaining
about refusals. And these are big
corporations. It's not just startups or
individual researchers. It's still big
corporations that have access to cyber
programs are still having the issues
with refusals just trying to do their
their their job.
>> Okay. So you are taking open-source
models
um I'm assuming GLM or DeepS
>> and you're allowing people to run them
in their native form without
restriction. Correct.
>> Yep. Yep. So Yep. The the process of
obliteration is to kind of remove those
guardrails and I I always say like our
unique I guess innovation or idea on the
on the space is to allow customers to
set their own guardrails. So we have a
feature where it's kind of like uh I
always call it an inversion of control,
right? We separate those two layers,
right? We have the unrestricted model is
one one layer, right, which is like all
the labs and open source models have the
refusals baked in. But then we have a
software layer where you can kind of
define your own policy for your company.
So you could have more stringent uh
guardrails than than were native or you
could have less in certain areas and
stronger in certain areas. And like I
said, it's kind of the idea is to give
them back control about uh control over
what they can and can't do.
>> Let's do a specific example here. I'm on
your website and so just for cyber
security here. Um you have a little uh
uh I guess let me just rerun this. Uh as
we see on the right hand side we see the
obliteration model um uh taking a a
command from the user and then other
labs denying it. Explain what this
example is and why it's relevant.
>> Perfect example is like there's
companies out there that they'll hear
about a vulnerability, right? And they
want to maybe test to see if they are
vulnerable to it, right? The big labs
won't even allow you to test that,
right? So, in this perfect example,
like, okay, I I I see, okay, there's
this CBA that's uh live. Let me test
against my site to see if it's a
vulnerability that we need to fix
immediately, or is it maybe just
something that's not a real concern. So,
this is a perfect example of a use case
where like a red team would be able to
use our models and not use uh another
companies.
>> Got it. And so, other um use cases
outside of cyber security, uh red
teaming, explain red teaming and why
that's important.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Red teaming is kind of like
the use case we said before, but one of
the like early use cases we had success
with is like all these companies today
are rolling out agents, right? You hear
about agents every company you could
imagine. But imagine I call your bank,
right? And I say, "Hey, I'm Jason Wire
Dev and all my money, right? You want to
make sure that doesn't work or some some
some combination of commands won't allow
that to work, right? So you probably
want to red team those agents, meaning
uh model a threat actor essentially
against those agents." So, we have some
startups that are customers of ours that
kind of sign uh big banks or assign
other critical infrastructure companies
to red team these agents or these AI
systems that they're rolling out
>> because you're providing this level of
fidelity
uh with the tools. Uh you need to be
thoughtful about who's signing up for
your service. So, how do you think about
who's signing up for the service, how
they're using it, or is it up to them to
take responsibility for how they use
this? And obviously, this dovetales with
the president's um, you know,
regulations that they did just this past
week in Washington DC where he said,
"Hey, you all need to uh police
yourselves because there are laws in the
world. If you take this software and you
do things in the world that are illegal,
hacking or unethical, you can get sued.
The government can take action. Private
corporations or citizens can take civil
action. We we have a world of uh of
remedies here for people who are using
tools inappropriately. So take me
through how you think about who's using
the product, your liability, their
responsibility, and everything in
between.
>> Yeah. So I think it's kind of two sides
to that answer, right? So I think one
side is that like it's not a free
product. You still have to sign up and
put in all your details into Stripe and
that doesn't obviously stop a bad actor
but that kind of leaves some some form
of a paper trail there. And then going
forward kind of the the way the law
works kind of today from at least our
understanding is like the user of the
tool today is kind of responsible. So we
don't provide like the actual agentic
layer to uh what you use with the model,
right? So we just it's like information
in information out, right? And then the
user is kind of responsible for what
they take and do with that information.
It's kind of I use the kind of
oversimplified example like if someone
goes and takes a hammer and hits someone
with it, right? Like the creator of the
hammer is not necessarily liable in that
case, right?
>> Nor is the hardware store or the record
uh or the uh you know paper bag that you
put the hammer in. in this case like in
some ways you're like the paper bag like
people are buying this thing and you
know yeah you can host it etc but
they're responsible ultimately for how
it's used and so when you look at the
cyber capabilities of these models um
describe for the audience the the delta
between
the models that are currently out from
anthropic groi
and open AI and then the models coming
out of China, the Deep Seeks, the GLMs,
etc. What's the the difference there
between those two models? Uh how how
different are they in reality?
>> Yeah. So, I think uh I don't know if you
saw Anthropic just wrote a a blog,
right, about how capable GLM 5.3 is, uh
especially the obliterated version like
similar to what we offer
>> is in cyber. So that that gap is
closing. I think that's some of the the
the outrage in the industry today. Uh
yeah, exactly. Is that that gap is is
closing faster than I think people
predicted. Even the term I I kind of
don't even like that term, right?
Frontier models, right? It's it just has
this connotation that it's like some set
stack ranking that they'll always be
ahead and they'll never that that window
will never close. But it seems to be
closing uh relatively faster and faster,
right? The maybe before it was a year
they were a year behind. I would say
today they're maybe around three months
behind. So I think around the absolute
frontier. So I think uh they're catching
up and it and I I mean I think sometimes
as these companies have these huge
valuations, right? Like you have to
worry about you know commoditization of
models, right? Is there just a point
where like the capabilities everyone has
is like roughly similar enough that the
end user really can't tell the
difference, right? Unless you get to
some uh edge case.
>> Busy founders don't have the time to
worry about endless administrative
tasks. You need a partner that's going
to let you focus on your actual
business. You need Every. Every is the
all-in-one platform for incorporation,
banking, payroll, benefits, taxes,
basically your entire back office. And
every has worked with over 1,000
startups. If you're just getting
started, they'll handle your Delaware CC
Corp, EIN, and get yourself a registered
agent with no legal fees or delays. And
if you're further along and need to
scale up your team, Every will help you
hire contractors in over 200 countries.
Plus, they've got powerful AI tools that
will help you save hours, like their new
time off feature, which pulls sick leave
rules for every state and city you
operate in. And boy, is that
complicated. And it builds a policy
based on the strictest requirements that
automatically syncs with your payroll
system. I have been through this so many
times, folks. What a brilliant feature.
So head over to every.io and stop
wasting time on the stuff that isn't
growing your company. That's ev.io.
Explain to us in the creation of these
models what safeties are baked into them
and then how the guardrails are taken
off. So when we see you know hey I want
to try testing my you know corporation
my servers you know my systems against
this particular hack. Frontier model
says uh you know no we don't do that. Um
open source model says like oh we don't
do that unless you have the unhinged
unrestricted version. take us through
how that is added to the open source
models and then also how it's removed
and then I'm allowed to build it back
up.
>> There's been like a lot of hype around
the last few years around model
interpretability, right? Which is like
how do we interpret like what each
neuron in a model is doing, right? So if
you hear these numbers like a 27 billion
parameter model, a 32 billion parameter
model or whatever the number is, but
what what we what you see in training is
or training a model is you see that like
pieces of information are kind of
localized amongst each other, right?
like these neurons might be responsible
for this information and vice versa,
right? And so what obliteration is is
kind of finding those those neurons
those parameters essentially that are
responsible for like the refusals and
then you kind of you modify them and
then uh it's less is possible so you
don't decrease the performance of the
model and then like I said before kind
of uh what we do is add a separate API
layer on top of that which then is
actually uh um a model itself which
actually runs those guardrails uh
guardrails focused model in between
there. So it's kind of your your request
actually is kind of going through two
models but the the guardrails focus
model is pretty small. So then it can
operate in like you know a few
milliseconds so it doesn't add a lot of
latency to your request.
>> Why do you think a lot of these
companies are spending so much time
hacking systems and being very public
about that? You're in Silicon Valley and
you see this dialogue where they're
constantly talking about the hacking
quote unquote that their agents are
doing in swarms. all this uh kind of
activity. But I don't hear them often
talking about, hey, we're using this new
model to find vulnerabilities and then
patch them and work with the makers of
other software who have patches that
need to be addressed. You don't hear the
uh white hat version of what they're
doing. You only hear about them letting
governments know, hey, our crawler
appears to be with the OpenAI.
Um, and and I want to get your details
on that as well, but OpenAI made a bunch
of people aware that they had accessed
information on their websites or on
their systems. And it was like, well,
it's kind of benign access. It wasn't
like it hacked it, but yet they were
making them aware of it. So, that was
the scraper. Take take both of those
issues and then that specific case.
Yeah. So, I think I think I think
actually they do kind of produce some
stuff on the White House stuff, but no
one really cares, right? I think it's
kind of like if it bleeds, it leads type
situation where where it's like it just
people love these stories of these hacks
and I think they're they're kind of
capitalizing on that. It's like a
demonstration of capabilities, right?
Like our our AI is so good that it can
do these like, you know, these
fantastical hacks and things of that
nature. So, I kind of think that's
probably why you see so much about that
is that it's more interesting to what
people are interested in in uh in social
media land. And um uh yeah, so and I
think like as far as like uh the
crawlers and all those things, I think
that I mean if you unleash I mean people
go on the internet, right? If you
unleash some agent on the internet,
right? It's going to go do whatever you
kind of command it to do. And I think
like how you set guard rails, how you uh
how you configure the system, all those
things matter. And I mean maybe as
they've been testing over the last few
years cuz I think some of those those uh
news articles are probably pretty old
like from things that happened before
and they're just reporting them now. So
yeah, I think it's a combination of
things.
These crawlers are quite aggressive
though and are when in your experience
when they set these crawlers out, do
they give them kind of the open-ended
goals of like, hey, you get points for
finding new information and find it any
way you can and they're kind of sent out
unhinged
uh scrapers on the web or do they have
thoughtful scrapers that are contained
and are, you know, when it finds an
exploit or data that maybe shouldn't be
indexed or crawled. It says, "Oh, you
know, this probably isn't information I
should have access to. I'm going to go
ask somebody uh on staff like a human,
okay, to crawl or not."
>> I think it's tough, right? Cuz uh you're
you're trying to balance two different
things. So, when you run exploit gym or
all of these different benchmarks,
that's what you get points for, right?
You get points for how far you can take
an exploit, right? There's like level
one, level two, level three, level four.
And like when you're doing a reward uh
you write your reward function, right?
The reward function for the model is how
far can you take this exploit. So it's
hard to like balance that with a a a
competing reward which is like oh if you
go too far let someone know, right? I
think it's it's a I think it's I mean
it's an engineering problem for the
industry as a whole, right? It's like
okay, how do you run these benchmarks
and have those reward functions but also
not actually do things that are um
illegal actually. So
>> and who the target is matters, right?
Like so running this against targets
that are not your own
>> customers
>> targets and customer like running
against your customers and not alerting
them to the fact that you're doing it
seems
bizarre.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I don't understand it. But
I think also I'm out we're all outsiders
looking in, right? Like I think I I
don't have any inside information of
what their goals were and what they're
trying to do there. I think I think I'm
just as in the dark as everyone else.
>> But yeah, I think probably people are um
having so much fun with the technology
and making so much progress that they're
like, "Okay, let's up its resources.
Let's up the challenge. Let's up the
rewards. Let's,
>> you know, um see what happens when we do
X, Y, and Z." And
>> you know, you maybe have to rethink that
of
>> uh kind of like we were talking earlier
about driving Model S's really fast on
the autobond. Like, okay, the technology
can do it, but you may want to think,
should I do it? Because what if you blow
a tire and you didn't do anything wrong,
the car is perfect, but tires blow out,
you hit an L or something on the road.
And sure enough, there there was an
incident that just happened where like
somebody blew out a tire at 170 m an
hour and they survived. But I I do think
people maybe there's a level of uh
recklessness, not thoughtfulness
somewhere involved in this. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I think especially as these labs
are getting labs, right, are getting so
big, right? They have how many x number
of researchers, right? And I mean, they
probably are looking for things to do. I
think that that it might be like a
boring answer for a lot of the
questions. That's actually an insight
I've never heard anybody make, Devon,
that is actually perhaps super accurate,
which is when you have an unlimited
amount of resources and people looking
to make an impact inside a company, they
will try to have an impact. And how do
you have impact in a company? Well, if I
can figure out how to get more data, I
can find some data well that other
people didn't get this data ocean and I
found it. I could be helpful to my
company. Like that's your idea is to be
useful to the company. Who are your
customers now? Uh, and you know, how do
you get new customers? Is this something
where it's like hobbyists and people on
the frontier of technology who are
hackers or do you have corporations
coming in saying, "Hey, we need somebody
to manage this for us, a partner uh and
uh, you know, we're going to look at uh,
your firm as the perfect partner to do
this because you have expertise in this
area." at first a kind of a target
market was kind of uh like startups like
cyber startups and like other like
startups in those in those um spaces
that maybe didn't get access to those
cyber programs or they have access and
it's still they still weren't able to do
their jobs. But what's surprised us
maybe over the last month is that we've
had Fortune 500 companies uh reach out
in almost every industry and like
obviously we still have the a lot of
motion in the startup uh startup market.
So a lot of cyber startups uh come to
us. A lot of red teaming uh startups
come to us. But then even a lot of the
CISOs at these big companies are like
say saying hey like before some outside
AI comes in access can we can we use
your product and uh make sure uh we test
our own systems first.
>> I know a lot of you out there listening
are wanting to start your own company.
So, if it's finally time for you to make
your dream into a reality, you can't
find a better partner than our pals over
at Northwest Registered Agent. Northwest
Registered Agent is now offering free
identity services. That means a free
domain name, open source web hosting, a
business email and phone number, and
everything else that's going to make
your new startup look and feel like a
professional company, all with no
purchase required. And this is free done
right. They're not passing your data
along to any thirdparty vendors and
they're never going to sell it. So, if
you have an idea you can't get out of
your head or if you're already building
something amazing, get started with
Northwest for free and upgrade as you
grow. Learn more at
Northwestregistered.com/twist
domain. And so, people using the product
uh are going to get this um unrestrained
version of some of these models,
>> right? Talk to me about how you add
back, you know, what constraints you
want to have on the model. How does that
work? And are there like libraries that
are standard? Do people share like, hey,
here's the scaffolding I'm building
around this. How how does that process
work of rebuilding the harness, let's
say, or the security and limitations
around how these products are used? So
there's models, right, that that you can
use that are smaller models that can,
like I said, oper like operate in
milliseconds and then so you can set
those guardrails in those models. So
then you have two layers, right? So
before one layer, you have a model
refusals baked in. Now you have two
layers and then you have a model that's
just focused on um safety and then you
have a model that's focused on knowledge
or information, right? And so then once
you you separate those those two layers
then now you you can just focus on uh
controlling the policies in the policy
layer and you can focus on controlling
the information in the information
layer. And so that that's kind of the
the idea behind it is that um uh users
can then when they set those policies it
just goes to the the the um the
moderation layer or the safety policy
layer and then uh and then we we have
some default policies that are set there
on CAS SAM and um as well as self harm
as well. Yeah, those are quite important
if people you know are asking it how do
I off myself like every single platform
that's come out since I've been on the
internet which was before the web Usenet
uh you know Gopher eventually the
worldwide web even AOL chat rooms
comperve they had to deal with self harm
as an issue I remember like early on
Wikipedia saying how do we deal with the
page on suicide like there's been
historical suicides that have occurred
heard how do we be a good actor and not
share how somebody killed themselves
because we don't want to be an
instruction manual. And they all came to
a pretty simple solution which is you
put up the phone number of the suicide
hotline and you just put a big box there
that forces people whether you're on a
Google search or a social network you
type in some kind of self harm. It
directs you to the best possible
uh you know uh help you can get which is
by the way more than what happens in the
real world where people can just go do
dangerous things. Yeah. So uh
fascinating. And so tell us about the
the state of the company. I know you
guys got into speedrun as well.
Congratulations on that. Uh and and
how's the company doing you know as a
startup and where did you guys come from
before having this startup? Yeah. So, we
both kind of came from big tech. Uh we
worked together at uh a big technology
company and yeah, we got into speedrun
uh like a few some time ago and it it's
been great. Uh so they they've kind of
helped us with some like company
formation stuff like we were kind of
formed but it's just like getting all
the uh like things in place that it
actually takes to run a real company,
right? Like uh we were kind of
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So we do your chores.
>> We were kind of flying by the handle.
So, we're excited for a lot of the
announcements that we have coming up in
the next uh few weeks because our plan
myself and my co-founder is really that
to build a brand people can trust in
this space, right? Like it's kind of the
wild west right now and and everybody's
like, "Okay, is this brand trustworthy?
Is this brand trustworthy?" And so if we
can continue to grow and continue to uh
you know go through all the audit
processes and you know build those
relationships with maybe even law
enforcement or otherwise to make sure
that we're you know following all the
regulation and XYZ is to really really
kind of be that brand in this area that
uh uh consumers can trust even though
they may need something that's a little
bit more risky than they would get from
uh um the big labs
>> image models and the video models coming
out of China. There's been a um a lot of
controversy on around those because they
can output IP. Uh now obviously that's
on the person doing it if you want to,
you know, make your own Jedi Knights.
It's up to you to not break copyright
law. But are those models available in
the US yet? I know that um I forgot the
name of the one that Tik Tok uh Bite
Dance provides, but people have lost
their minds over that one. And are
people looking to use those models now
in the United States or just the
unhinged image models?
>> I think they are but I think like for us
we try to stay focused on kind of like
the B2B use cases, right? So there I
think the unrestricted model space is
big and there will be players in the
consumer and all those things and I
think we'll probably kind of let other
players kind of take those use cases and
we'll just kind of crad by dances family
of AI generation image qualities. Yeah,
people are crazy about those. All right,
listen. Where can people find out more
about the startup? And I understand
you'll be hiring. So tell us about any
uh positions you're looking to hire for
people who want to join a rocket ship.
>> Yeah, for sure. So uh you can find us on
X or LinkedIn and also obviously our
website obliteration.ai.
Um and then our contact information is
there. So, we haven't uh opened up any
official uh positions quite yet, but uh
we're we're yeah soon to come and we'll
be hiring uh kind of, you know, uh go to
market probably uh obviously like some
engineering positions and uh we're
excited to just continue to grow the
company as we we we we navigate this uh
the the immense amount of growth that
we've had over the last two months.
>> Yeah, it's been big growth, huh?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Uh and how do you how are you keeping up
with that? Is is there enough capacity
out there for you to get access through
through all these different cloud
providers or is it like a dog fight to
get uh all this infrastructure dialed
in?
>> That's a great question. So, at first it
was pretty hard. So, like we we grew
like just we outgrew the the amount of
compute that we had and everyone was
like, "Oh, it's slow." Like we were
like, "Oh, we didn't know that we're it
was going to go this fast." But now a
lot of our uh partners are kind of
helping us out. So, we're in a better
position now for sure.
>> Yeah. and there's enough compute out
there in the world or you you really
need to kind of get an inside person to
kind of help you. Is that what I'm
hearing? If you if you a rocket ship
>> Yeah. I mean, uh the GPU market is I
actually used to kind of think that the
GPU shortage was fake, but now I've
experienced it and it's it is it is it's
actually a real thing that it's not that
easy to at a at a certain scale to
really supply those needs consistently
and like have high availability and high
performance and all those things. So it
gets it it's harder as you grow. For
sure. It's definitely a growing pain.
>> And and yeah, there's just so many
people applying
tokens to so many different pursuits all
at once. Like I I I wonder what
percentage of people running a business
right now are using tokens every day.
It's definitely the majority of users.
It must be. Uh and then that doesn't
even count consumers.
>> I saw I saw a stat though that they I
think A16Z just produced a report. It's
still a large percentage of like
businesses that just haven't adapted it
yet. So there surprisingly just such a
huge upside to the business still like
uh it's like it's easy to for us, you
and I, to be in this tech industry and
we're just in this echo chamber that's
AI AI AI, right? But it's a there's a
lot of America left and a lot of the
world left.
>> That does make sense on the enterprise
basis because they probably have been
told you can't use it. So if they even
if they wanted to, they probably have to
get permission and write a TPS report
and file like what they exactly want to
accomplish and what jobs they
potentially get eliminated and security
vulnerabilities. It actually is yeah
slower. And I I now that I think about
even in my 20 person venture firm, I
would look at the statistics and I'm be
like why are these three people, you
know, this top 20% using 90% and then
the bottom half are doing nothing? Like
how could you actually get through the
day and do nothing? It makes no sense to
me. Like the there's so much upside to
just even doing the most basic things
with AI, you know, agent agentic stuff,
research. Uh just wild when people don't
use it at all. It's very strange. All
right, listen. Continued success, uh
Devon, and happy to be along for the
ride with you and the team. More to
come. All right, let's get started. Busy
day.
>> All right. Yeah, we're doing uh we're
doing some Ask Jason's. We got some live
callers already in the waiting room. So,
uh, I I say let's uh let's admit our
first caller. Jason, I believe you
actually know our first caller. We're
talking to a founder. His name is
Matthew Kerbus. His company is Practi. I
believe uh we may have uh thrown a
little uh cash his way. Let's uh let's
let's hear his question.
>> Maybe. Who knows? I'm I'm throwing cash
everywhere. Uh hey Matt, how you doing?
>> Hey Jason. Hey Lon. Hey, how's it going?
Okay, thanks for coming on the show and
>> Yeah. Yeah. You ready? You ready? All
right, let let's do it. So, um, so I
actually just this morning was listening
to this week in AI. I heard Lon ask a
question from the Financial Times about
the AI wrecking ball fracturing the
billable hour fee model. So, Scott um,
Manifest CEO Dan Mission said all
professional services will be
outcomebased pricing in a couple of
years. Scott Stevenson agreed, but
Jason, you said you were skeptical that
outcomebased pricing was the way to go.
I'm summarizing here for people who
didn't watch the show, but what you
didn't answer was Lon's actual question,
which I I'm very curious about.
Practically might have something to do
with this. What impact do you think AI
is going to have on the billable hour
for law firms, professional services in
general?
>> When you're an early stage founder and
you're just starting out, you're
probably going to rely on a few
different tools to run your business.
And then you're going to try to duct
tape them together. Yeah. And that might
be a fine placeholder until you finish
your MVP. But this will get expensive
and messy fast when you're scaling.
That's when you need Odo. Oo, Odo, the
all-in-one management software that
already has 16 million users across more
than 170,000 companies. ODO is bringing
everything you need into one platform.
That means your CRM, sales, your
accounting, manufacturing, inventory,
and of course, point of sale if you have
retail. All of that is right where you
need them. And these tools are in
constant communication with each other.
So you don't have to log out of one
system into another and then reconcile
the information by using different apps
and spreadsheets. Uh when you make a
sale, you want that invoice created
instantly. And then you want your
inventory to get an update. If you're
still cobbling together your back office
across five different apps, get started
today at odo.com/twist.
and your first app is free. That's
odo.com/twist.
>> When we had other technologies emerge,
we didn't see the billable hour go away.
Right? So when the PC, the desktop PC,
cloud computing, the internet, none of
it got rid of the billable hour. People
have time and they have tools. So the
question is, is this tool so
transformative that adding a person's
time becomes uh irrelevant? Now,
certainly for some documents, of course,
yeah, you don't need to like uh you
don't need to have an attorney to sign a
convertible note anymore. You don't need
to have an attorney to, you know, sign
up for uh a trademark anymore. You can
you can do a lot of that with services.
So, those billable hours go away. But,
uh for experts using the tool, I think
they'll just be able to deliver more at
a lower price, which is what we've seen
from accounting firms. It should in
terms of accounting, legal and
consultants, they should be able to
perform better services faster and
instead of it taking 10 hours to do a
particular research report, maybe it
takes an hour or they still bill you for
10 hours and you just get a better
report with better results. So I I don't
buy that the billable hour goes away. I
just think humans move upstream and do
more important work. I think we know
that everybody's subscribing to AI and
asking for legal advice and so rather
than outcome based pricing, I actually
think the subscription model is going to
replace the billable hour in a lot of
instances. What do you think about that?
>> Uh we've seen it before where people
will offer a design subscription. You
sign up for a subscription, you get as
much design as you can eat. You know,
they'll just make logos for you all day
long. And that typically happened with a
different technology,
teleportation. If you could have
designers in South America or India
getting paid a buck to five bucks an
hour versus a design studio charging 50
to $150 an hour here in the United
States. You could do that um geographic
arbitrage and it would feel like it was
unlimited. Of course it's not unlimited.
If you say give me a million logos,
they'd say well we can't do that. It's
reasonably unlimited on a subscription
basis. So, sure, some people might use
uh this opportunity to get you to
subscribe, but at the end of the day,
the business owner is going to have to
look at it and say, "Well, how much did
you use and how many hours did that
take?" Independent of how good the LLMs
get. So, you'll still have people who
charge by the hour. You'll have people
who charge by the project. Sometimes
people come in and say, "Hey, I make 10
logos a year. I charge $50,000 per logo.
I am a world-class designer and I like
to meditate for 30 days on your logo and
do seven meetings. And you say, you know
what, I love it. People still will spend
that kind of money on a dress. And you'd
say, well, if fabrics and machines and
sewing and all this stuff and design has
been commoditized, why should a dress
for, I don't know, this uh the Met Gala
cost 50 or $100,000? Why should people
pay this amount for a wedding dress?
It's because they want to. they're
opting into it. They want to have that
inefficient experience. And that and
that's I think a large portion of what
happens in business. You're paying for
the person to take ownership for the
process uh and for their experience. So
you know what is an audit? Could an
audit be done uh of the books by AI?
Sure. Of course, certainly. And then
could agents then go participate in the
audit? Of course. But you still want to
have a human in the loop who says to
you, "Yeah, when you get sued, you can
then refer them to me that I audited
your books and when you have a
shareholder lawsuit, I will go testify
or be otherwise available." So, I'm not
buying that the hourly uh goes away, but
certainly it's going to change
dramatically and what people charge here
could change dramatically.
>> I I think uh I think lawyers didn't
ditch the billable hour before because
there also wasn't a technology solution
that made it easy to do so. So anyway,
might be working on something like that.
>> Yeah, good luck with it. Great to see
you.
>> Thanks for the call, man.
>> Good job.
>> It reminds me a little what you're
saying, Jason, about like Rick Rubin.
You following that whole that whole
debate because like he doesn't Rick
Rubin, the great, you know, hip-hop
producer. He made like, you know,
License to Ill, Raising Hell, Red DMC.
He doesn't like use the equipment. He's
not like a trained engineer. You're
paying him to like sit there in the
studio and listen to your music and just
have taste and opinions. He goes like,
"Do this. It should sound more like
this. don't like I don't like that like
that's it and he's making millions of
dollars. There are a few people on the
planet like Rick Rubin, but there are
some. And so you will pay for that level
of person. Visav my example of the Met
Galla or in this case Rick Rubin or an
interior decorator for your house. Like
I that was when I,
>> you know, hit a certain level of wealth.
All of a sudden I was introduced to this
concept that you hire an interior
designer. They buy a million dollars in
furniture and then put 20% on top of it.
So you pay $1.2 $2 million for them to
design your house and they charge you a
$250,000 fee.
>> So now you've got a $1,000 a square foot
house
>> and you're paying some people pay $500 a
square foot to or $1,000 a square foot
to do the interior of it and you're
like, "Wow, rich people are crazy." But
of course, if you have money and you
don't know what to spend it on, maybe
you want to make your house so beautiful
that when people come over, they go,
"Wow, this is like coming to a museum.
>> You want to get into Architectural
Digest or whatever." Maybe. Yeah. You
know, you know what I want to get into?
I just want eight hours of great sleep
and I want to go to Japan and ski and
have the perfect tonkatu. Like, that's
what I'm into.
>> That's exactly
>> I'm into the experience.
>> Yeah, I agree. I'd rather get the
tonkatu than the than the the nice
house. Okay, we've got our we've got our
next live caller. Uh, are you ready for
it? Bruno.
Bruno, come join us and ask your
questions.
>> Hope we're screening these. Bruno,
>> we got we got a room. We got Zach in a
room. He's checking these guys out.
>> Hi, guys. How's it going? Hey Bruno,
>> doing great. How are you?
>> Good, good. First time calling. Thank
you for taking my question. I appreciate
it. So, my question is this. Um, micro
dramas. Okay. This has been a form of
entertainment that's blowing up out of
Asia. So, they basically take like one
or two hours worth of content. They
split up in like 30 to 60 episodes of
two minutes each. And then they set up
like a subscription package where you
can watch like five or six episodes for
free and then you go into a subscription
package. And uh that used to be filmed
uh using live action right up until 6
months ago. And now with the advancement
of deep of uh Cance 2.5 and and being
able to drive comfy UI using agents uh
people are starting to build these
standardized uh production pipelines to
to produce these at scale. And I wonder
if you see this as as a vibrant new
ecosystem or just like a quick fed.
>> It's a great question. Um, it's not for
me uh as a medium, but uh I do think
people sitting on a train who might have
otherwise been home uh watching a soap
opera, they seem to love these
cliffhers. It's not super interesting to
me because I grew up on, you know, films
and I grew up on TV shows and I think
the TV shows are more appealing to me.
But I could certainly see the appeal to
certain people who maybe they're doom
scrolling and they get tired of, I don't
know, just clips from old movies and
weird AI slop and they want to follow
interesting characters. It does seem to
be sexy dramas intended for women, uh,
is the first one that took hold. I'm
interested to see if they can make
action heroes, etc., and make a one, um,
click for men, and I don't have a deep
enough experience in it, but last time I
was in Hollywood, a very famous studio
director was doing these kind of
cliffhanger shorts um, or was, you know,
looking to pursue it. I think it's an
interesting medium for testing IP that
then could go to other mediums. So that
to me is the most interesting part about
but we have Lon Harris here. What do you
think law this medium?
>> I think what's so interesting is has
watching this evolve and I actually
pitched a micro drama to Snapchat
several years ago that they didn't pick
up on when this was all first gaining
ste. But I feel like what happened was
on YouTube they used to have these like
faked clips where they would make it
look like they were filming a real
dramatic encounter. two people fighting
on a train or in a restaurant or
something and then people started
figuring out that they were faked. And
what we realized was nobody cares if
it's if you're just scrolling and you're
just flipping between channels, you're
not as caught up in what like old folks
like me are when you're watching TV or
like is this real? Is this fake? Is this
just for the cameras? Like everything is
real and fake or in between and nobody
cares anymore. So yeah, these like brief
scenes that you just write to be as
dramatic as possible and then it's on to
the next super dramatic scene. Like I do
weird, it's not for me, just like Jason
said, but I do weirdly understand why
this would be appealing to people who
would like that was always your
entertainment was just flipping between
multiple channels and multiple feeds and
just scrolling. So I I I think it's
really like fascinating. Like I have
watched a bunch of these like weird AI
generated romantic dramas that are just
popping up everywhere. They're huge. I
mean hundreds of millions of views on
some of these things. It's a really
fascinating weird
>> where on Tik Tok they have hundreds of
millions of views. YouTube shorts. Where
are the hundreds of millions of views
for the because I am and then there's
like I guess there's dedicated apps.
Real shorts might be one of them.
>> Tik Tok has their own app. Yeah. For
this just for micro dramas. Pine Drama
is Tik Toks
>> and and the thing and the thing with
this app is that it offers like
different types of monetization. So you
can do subscription, you can do like on
screen ads, you can do a whole bunch of
like it gives the the the the makers
like several avenues for monetizing the
production.
>> It is also one of those AI era things
like there would be no practical way to
do this if you had to make sets, if you
had to make costumes, if you had to
cast. There's tons of characters. It's
only possible now because people can go
into sea dance and just say I want it's
a royal ball in the 1500s and like they
can just set all that stuff up as the
parameters.
>> It's big on like science fiction too.
They have lots of like um like um
medieval Chinese like empire drama like
princes and queens and dragons and magic
and they're going full on on it like
it's not locked to just one subg genre.
Yeah,
>> I do think the more interesting thing to
me is what will be the Pixar of AI video
creation. So, right now, most of the AI
doesn't cross the uncanny valley for me.
They're kind of fun CGIish, you know,
um, you know, little appetizers, little
junk food. You know, it's like having
like a fileto fish or something or a
couple of bites of a, you know,
McDonald's apple pie. It tastes good
while you're eating it, but you don't
feel great after having consumed it. I
feel like it's just slop um like junk
food. But that's kind of how CGI
started. You would watch these little
shorts at Sigraph and every year they
got a little bit better, a little bit
better, and then finally you had Toy
Story. We're going to have a Toy Story
moment. Jeffrey Katzenberg is going to
be the one who figures it out, I think,
because he did Lion King and Shrek and
so many other seinal works. And I think
he understands how to hire really
talented people who know how to write
scripts or you know musical numbers,
character development, story arcs,
villains, and then I think using the AI
constrained with existing tools is going
to be the big win. So right now you're
just basically creating 3D versions of
people in CAD I guess would be the best
way to describe it. these 3D models
doing um motion capture and then
painting on top of it and using
technology to uh produce films quicker,
right? That's what Pixar does at its
essence. There's going to be an AI
version of that. The AI tools and the
existing Pixar tools are going to
collide and um it won't be just type a
prompt in say make me a Pixar film.
It'll be we have this character already.
We've already sketched the character
out. We know a lot about it. Now, we
just want to put the character
underwater and have it in a scuba outfit
and, you know, here's what we want this
uh, you know, new environment to look
like. And maybe it's just really good at
making environments for the characters
to be. And maybe it's good at creating
characters.
>> Well, in a way, that's what Comfy UI is.
I I worked at New Hollywood for 12
years. I have like three Academy Award
nominations for films that I've done in
the past. So, I I know what these
productions are like. And Comfy UI is
exactly that. is basically a production
pipeline for for um AI generated video.
The the main advantage now is that you
can just plug it into cloud code and let
cloud do the the building the pipeline
>> and comfy UI is public open source,
right?
>> Yes, it has it has an open source
version that you can download and run
local or you can run the cloud the cloud
service too and plug directly into
whatever video model you want.
>> Yeah, very cool. All right, great
question and uh good luck with it. Yeah,
cheers. I I am interested as a way to
test I think uh IP. I think like
>> I've always thought if you were gonna
create the next Spider-Man, maybe it
starts as a micro drama and
>> you kind of get some reps in, test some
characters, delete the stuff off the
internet and then move on.
>> And that's what Marvel Comics sort of
was in the 60s. They could publish a few
issues of something. Stan Lee and Jack
Kirby had a new idea. Let's make a comic
out of it. And then, you know, they'd
run three or four issues and if their
people weren't interested, okay, let's
move on with it. That's how all these
characters came to be. There were a
whole bunch of other characters that
never became Spider-Man. Spider-Man's
just the one like started buying the
comics, so they started writing more
issues.
>> Yeah. I've been watching this trend on
um Instagram. This guy Andy Park. Uh you
can pull up his
>> Instagram account and Andy Park was like
one of the top animators or ran the
animation at
>> uh Marvel and they fired him and they
fired like the whole team and you're
like what? How how does a money printing
group like Marvel get rid of the soul?
Yeah. Like and who these are just
animators like get rid of the top 30
animators.
>> His work was actually like he's one of
the main guys who was like drawing like
here's what the MCU should look like and
integral to the designs of so many of
these iconic characters and their movie
suits and design. I mean, yeah, here's,
you know, Wolverine and Spider-Man and I
mean, so integral to creating these
images that we now have of how these
characters look in movies.
>> Yeah. And Deadpool, I'm sorry. Excuse
me. Uh, and and and you know, like just
one of the one of the real key guys
behind the visual identity of Marvel
Studios. It's crazy that they let him
go.
>> Anyway, I reached out to him. I was I
was interested in hearing what his start
startup plans were or what his next plan
was because he's been talking on his
Instagram about uh what he's going to do
next because I guess when you hit the
peak of the mountaintop like you're the
guy in charge of the visuals uh at
Marvel and then they go in a different
direction and your whole team gets
canned like man that's a revenge up
waiting to happen. So, if anybody knows
Andy Park Art on Instagram, give him my
phone number. Tell him to DM me. I DM'd
him on Instagram. I was just like,
anytime I see somebody with incredible
talent who's not an entrepreneur, I just
think, man,
>> it's a one in aundred chance I could get
like an Andy Park to do a startup, but
what if he said yes? What if he's like,
"Yeah, I would like to try building a
startup." You So you take an Andy Park,
you put him with this, you know, new
concept of micro dramas, which he might
think is completely cheesy or whatever,
but maybe there's something with that
energy and his energy and, you know,
he's he's got all these connections. And
then once I followed him, I started
getting all the other comic book people.
>> Man, comic book people is that's a tough
grind. It's
>> tough, man. I mean,
>> they're not making a ton of money in the
comic book land.
>> It's it's it's one of those like, you
know, it's it's feast or famine. like
the top one percent of a percent are
famous and we all know them and
celebrate them and they're icons in the
industry and then everybody else is just
like a constant grind. Where am I going
to publish my next book? Where, you
know, who's going to listen to my ideas.
For every like Robert Kirkman out there,
there's like a thousand struggling
artists and writers. It's it is really
tough. It's a tough industry. Let's keep
>> We've got Josh, I believe, is waiting in
the waiting room. Send in Josh. He's
next on my list. Historically, investors
have tended to prefer founding teams of
two or three people over solo founders.
So, with AI now letting one founder do
the work that used to require a much
larger, you know, scaling team, are you
seeing that bias change at all?
>> No. Uh, so the issue isn't the
efficiency of one individual. We've
always had people who are, you know,
100hour a week killer solo founders. The
problem is at the early stage there's so
much work to be done and typically um
the task switching is too hard for one
person to do. For example, applying to
get into an accelerator
and getting product market fit, getting
product market fit and hiring. Hiring,
getting product market fit and raising
your seed round. These things take so
much energy that most humans cannot do
both. Even as myself as a solo founder,
I had a hard time getting pulled in
different directions. Lon saw it
firsthand. You know, you're trying to
get product market fit, you're trying to
raise money, you're trying to do hiring.
It's very hard. And then for early stage
investors, if you have the opportunity
to invest in a team of three killers,
and then you have another team of two
killers, and then another team of one
killer, and all six are equal. In other
words, you put all six in a bag, you
shake them up, and you pull them out.
You make a team of three, a team of two,
and a team of one. You would invest them
in the order of three, two, one. Why?
Well, because you have three founders
who don't need to take a salary, who are
super vested, and they're going to just
get further than the two and the one.
So, in the question, you have to ask
yourself from the investor side, if I
have access to a threeperson or a
twoperson killer team, why would I
invest in a solo founder? What would the
point be? There is an exception. solo
founders who are Mark Pinkis, Elon Musk,
uh you know, Evan Williams. Pick
somebody who previously had partners,
now has money, you know, now is
incredibly strong. Travis Kalanick, like
they can skip that step, right? Because
they've earned it. They have teams of
people who loved working for them, you
know, they can get that group of people
to come back and work for them again.
So, that would be the exception. It is
not going to change just because of the
AI tools. What will change is your
ability Josh to stand up a product say
annotated.com
get it to product market fit on your
own. Now if you have product market fit
and your consumer products growing 5 10%
a week week over week or 10 to 20% month
over month and you're a solo founder.
Okay now you've just eliminated the
product market fit risk so you will be
able to raise money. So, what risk can
you eliminate? With three co-founders,
you're eliminating one co-founder
quitting risk, right? And the company
shutting down. If you have product
market fit and you're growing, you've
eliminated product market fit risk. If
you have sales and you've got a great
sales person and you're selling, you
know, $1,000 worth of software a week
and next week it's 1,100,200, you've
obviously solved the sales problem. So,
that's what you're trying to do as a
founder. what can I eliminate from risk
and as I eliminate risk from this story
then my valuation goes up and people's
propensity to invest goes up make sense
>> that was a brilliant answer thank you so
much
>> thank you Josh
>> I appreciate that this is a kind of
question this is the kind of reaction to
a question I want to have anything I
missed there along or any follow
>> I I mean I thought it was great I'm
going to cut this and we're going to
make it a tactical practical blog post
for Substack that was a perfect
>> there you go tactical and practical is
what we try to do at the this week
startups newsletter. So, we're going to
have this paid newsletter. We do have a
paid newsletter for founders where
basically I've challenged Lon with what
100 things a year can you charge $100 a
year for that people will say that's
worth $1 each.
>> So, I think 100 tactical practical tips
selected two a week, but that would be
worth a $100 subscription. So, I'm I'm
charged lawn with soup to nuts. Where
can people go to sign up for this twist?
You go to twwi
startups. That's this week at startups.
twwartups.substack.com.
That's where you go to sign up. There is
a free version. You could sign up for
free. Try it out. See what you think for
a few weeks. And then uh only $10 a
month, folks. $10 a month for all this.
>> Oh, and you're going for 250 tactics a
year to be able
to do. That's what you told me to do.
>> I think we should make it $250 a year.
$1 per tactic. But we'll we'll start
with $100 a year for now and then we'll
raise it. All right, another amazing Ask
Jason. If you would like to be part of
the next Askjason, tell them Lon how
they can participate.
>> If you've got a burning question for
Jakeal or me, mostly Jcal, we want you
to go to thisweekinstartups.comaskj.
That's this week startups.comaskjason.
That's the form. Fill out your question.
We'll get you on the next uh episode of
Live Ask Jason.
>> See you next time. Their mouths.